<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

   	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp1">Capricorn is an App to show up to 8 different system resources.
		This system resources can be shown also on homescreen with widgets.</string>
	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp2">
		Possibilities to display:\n\n1. With the App.\nFor that you can select the required category via tabs.
		To update the data in the current view simply press the button "Update".
		The font size in the App can be adapted in the settings independently from the font size of the widgets.

	</string>
	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp3">
		2. With widgets.\nThis is the main use case of Capricorn. There are 3 different widget sizes available.
		With 3 (2 columns), 5 (3 columns) or 7 (4 columns) different display options, which can be configured independently.
		All widgets on homescreen are one row high.
	</string>

	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp4">
		The widgets are scalable horizontally and vertically (if supported by the device and the system).
		If the system scaling does not work, manual scaling is possible. The icons automatically scale with the widget size.
		The font size can be adjusted.
	</string>
	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp5">Supported system resources:\n
			- Current battery level in \u0025\n
			- Free memory of RAM in (GB, MB, KB, Byte)\n
			- Free internal memory in (GB, MB, KB, Byte)\n
			- Free external memory (removable SD card) in (GB, MB, KB, Byte)\n
			- Usage of mobile data\n
			- Usage of free minutes and SMS if necessary\n
			- Add SMS to free minutes if supported by contracts\n
			- Transmitted WIFI data</string>
	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp6">
			- Overall CPU usage in \u0025\n(unfortunately does not work on Android 8.0 (Oreo) devices. The app shows \u0022n/w\u0022 instead)\n
			- Screen brightness as the value from the slider of the settings menu. The real value can be different if automatic brightness is selected.\n
	</string>
	<string name="pref_GeneralHelp7">To evaluate the usage of free minutes, the app needs access to telephone data and SMS.
		Capricorn neither starts calls nor sniffes calls and even does not send or read SMS.
		The data are only be used to calculate free minutes correctly.</string>

	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp1">Settings for cost relevant data (calls \u0026 data)\n\nCapricorn
		does not gather any personal data from any source of the device or from the provider.
		It calculates all data only by the values done in the settings and by the data provided by the device.
	</string>
	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp2">That means for mobile and WIFI data, that the device provides data until the last system boot.\nFor
		calls Capricorn reads out the data from the call log.
		If this will be cleared, Capricorn can not calculate data regarding calls.</string>

   	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp3">For a correct calculation it is necessary to make some inputs:\n\n
   	    											- How shall the calculation been done\n \u0009\u002D\u002D without correction\n \u0009\u002D\u002D with reference value\n \u0009\u002D\u002D with the billing period by your provider\n
													- Date of the next cycle change\n
													- Time period (monthly, 30-days)\n
													- Activation of data monitoring\n
	</string>
   	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp4">	  \u0020- View of used or left data\n
													- High speed limit for mobile data (or personal max value if no flat)\n
													- Already used data, if the start of the measurement is within a running cycle</string>
	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp5">	- Activation of calls monitoring\n
											- View of used or left free minutes\n
											- Number of free minutes (or personal max value if no free minuntes or calls flat)\n
											- Already used free minutes, if the start of the measurement is within a running cycle</string>
	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp6">Used data and calls are positiv on the widget, left data and calls are negativ on the widget.\n\nIf
											monitoring of data and calls is activated, the widget shows the usage during the pilling period with a green dot
	    									if the usage is within a linear calculated range.</string>
	<string name="pref_CostRelDataHelp7">Exeeds the current usage the calculated limit Capricorn shows a red dot.</string>

	<string name="pref_WlanHelp1">The app always shows the sum of sent and received data.
		You can use different start values:\n\nStart values of WIFI-data:</string>
	<string name="pref_WlanHelp2">With an input of a valid value (0 to 9999 TByte) Capricorn shows the WIFI data from this time plus the Start value.\n\nWith
		an input of „1 Byte“ Capricorn does not make any calculation and shows the transmitted WIFI data since the last system boot.
	</string>
	<string name="pref_WidViewPosHelp1">The position of the views in the widget can be freely defined. The larger versions takes the settings of the smaller ones.</string>
	<string name="pref_WidViewPosHelp2">- 2x1 -> 1 to 3 (small)\n- 3x1 -> 1 to 5 (medium)\n- 4x1 -> 1 to 7 (large)\n</string>
	<string name="pref_CurValHelp1">All Resourcen can also been shown in the app.
		The resources are clustered in groups general, data, calls, WIFI and network.\nWith buttons you can select the category.</string>
	<string name="pref_CurValHelp2">The values can be updated with a corresponding button.</string>


</resources>